So when I make this kind of bed board or something like that, I draw a hard board with a piece of paper and then modify some of its dimensions and the thickness to complete the construction of its thickness.
In other words, it's lazy. After adding the thickness, this board will have a certain thickness.
And then at this time, I think its round corner is a little too round, so I might go to reduce its edge curve.
And then by adjusting its thickness, we can adjust the thickness of this board.
And then after I finish this thickness, I will draw the inner line for it, and then cut these boards according to what I want.
Actually, you can do these steps in other 3D software.
It's just that I usually just open an AMD, and I don't open other 3D software.
So basically, these are all different ways.
Right?
This is how the board is finished.
And then through a different thickness, we can make this kind of old-fashioned bed board.
The material of the wooden board.
And then I'll go back and continue to make some adjustments to its edge.
And then by positioning,
I'll directly place a board on top of this board.
It's this pattern.
There's a pattern that looks like a star.
And then I'll use the board to match it.
After I finish making a bed board, I'll think about making the bed board.
And then...
Eh?
Oh, I'm ugly!
I'm ugly!
Right?
This is what you call being ugly.
You canOL is ugly.
This is how ugly you are, right?
FoeIyEyEyEyEyEyEyEyEyEyEy.
O2O, I'm so hungry, just look at me.
FoeIyEyEyEyEyEyEyEyEyEyEyEy.
FoeIyEyEyEyEyEyEyEyEyEyEyEyEyEyEy, whoo.
FoeIyEyEyEyEyEyEyEyEyEyEy.
I will draw some inner lines to create this kind of effect
Yes, MD doesn't know what to do
You can do all kinds of things in MD
After drawing the inner lines
I will adjust its position a little bit
Look at its...
Anyway, just look at it
I remember someone used MD to make a...
It seems like it was Zhang Yu
Zhang Yu?
Yes, yes, yes
Oh, it's Shui Mu
Oh, I seem to have an impression
I've seen people making umbrellas or something like that
And I just saw the feedback you gave
It seems like it's time for a glove tutorial
When I have time
I can make a glove when I prepare for the next live stream
But...
It's not the same as the last live stream
Oh, I've put some pressure on it
After I put some pressure on it
It will have this kind of effect
The content of the next live stream should be a new feature
Next time
The next time will probably be Christmas
Then I will reduce the particle diameter of the created version
Why reduce the particle diameter?
It's because when the particle diameter is 20
Some wrinkles are not visible
Then I will put some pressure on it
It will make the result look like this
After I put some pressure on it
And then after reducing the particle diameter
The version that has been created
It will have this kind of pung-pung effect
Using MD to make a high-end
I can try it
But I have thought about it
It's better to make it with other 3D graphics
Then I keep adjusting its rendering thickness
I know that there is a gap in the middle, so I keep adjusting the thickness and the thickness of the conflict.
In general, after adding pressure, we all have to raise the tension of the corner line, otherwise, like the one I created just now, it is not so obvious.
After you raise the tension of the corner line, because it is difficult to pull in the direction of the corner line, it is easier to come out like this.
Then
What should I do next?
Let me think about it.
Oh, I seem to think that this piece in the middle always feels empty.
I'm looking at what's going on.
How can this be empty in the middle?
Then I stopped recording.
I went to find a reason.
Oh, and then I remembered.
Because when I didn't record it, I turned off its border curve.
I think there are some long ends.
Because I saw the reference picture, there is no curve in the middle of its long end.
I turned off the border curve.
Then I thought about it.
I was thinking about how to solve it.
Oh, I've done this step.
How can I adjust it again?
It's too late.
I turned on the border curve.
So lazy.
Then we will pour this bed sheet out in the form of OBJ.
And then I wanted to write all in English.
But I remembered the kind of bedhead.
It's because I can't remember.
I'll play Pinyin.
Then when I pour it out, I will choose to pour it out as multiple goals.
So that we can adjust its texture or other things later.
It's more convenient.
Then if you pour it out, you can pour out the thickness of the border curve.
Why am I pouring this board out now?
Because we all know that the board is in MD.
In fact, the collision between the board and the board is the center of the board.
If we want it to have a collision with the entire bed and other things,
we have to pour it out and then pour it in the form of a virtual model again.
So I'll pour it out and pour it in again after I'm done with the MD.
Can't such an old bed be sold in a furniture store?
Don't.
If you can't sell it to me, I can buy it myself.
My bed should be changed.
Then after the bed is done.
In fact, there are many things that can be done in MD.
I remember that I used to make all kinds of things.
What necklace?
It's all right.
Then I put some OBJ in it.
After that, I thought that my bed was wrong no matter how I looked at it at that time.
I found something behind me.
I forgot to sit on the corner of the bed.
I said, why does this bed feel wrong?
I found that it was floating on the ground.
Then I sat on that bed.
I was sitting on the corner of the bed.
Then I went to study the corner of the bed.
Many of them have a ball shape.
I don't know why.
Anyway, there is a ball.
I just put a ball in it.
Then I used a glue to stick it on the board.
Then I transformed it.
I finally know how to make those bottles and jars with MD.
How to do it.
Yes.
Because I'm too lazy.
I can do anything in MD.
I just use MD to do it.
I mainly saw this competition.
I saw that there was a person in this MD competition.
He did it all over the world.
All MD did it.
I said, wow, it's so strong.
Yes.
In fact, some of us usually watch other people's videos to know.
Oh, it turned out to be like this.
I can do it like this.
I used to use MD to make a lamp out of cloth.
Then the lamp was next to another software in our company.
It was used by him.
It was used by him to show.
I think it's okay.
It's this kind of weird thing.
MD does this thing really.
I think it's fast.
I think it's very MD.
I think it's the fastest thing to do.
I think.
Yes.
Because for me, this is a relatively simple model.
Then it may be good to do it directly in MD.
Then I will put this model back to life.
Because sometimes I often point to them.
And plus the model has its own network.
When my company was recording, the computer was a bit lagging.
I put all of them back to life.
Then create a version.
Then in fact, because I added a speed to the video I recorded in advance.
Originally, it still takes some time.
Then just draw a version.
Let it drop on our bed.
Because I want to do one.
I was looking at the reference picture.
Generally speaking, this kind of bed will be wrapped.
That is, the bed sheet will be wrapped outside the bed.
Then I was thinking about how to solve this problem.
Because most people will put the factory electricity out of that piece.
Put it under the battery.
So I'm there.
Start from a small seat.
Do it little by little.
This kind of general is to put it manually.
Is it estimated?
Not.
Not?
Yes.
I am lazy.
Use a very lazy method.
Just add it first.
Then I add it while I think.
What should I do with this thing?
Then when I recorded the video.
I recorded a very long section.
Add a little bit.
OK.
Learn a little.
Anyway, what I can think of is to manually give it.
Use that pin to pin it up.
Then squeeze the heart out.
Yes.
The method I use is very simple.
The reason why I expanded this version of the film.
Because I want it to look like a box.
Shown outside.
But failed.
Because after I sewed it.
I feel like there is something wrong.
This board is too long.
Then it is wrapped outside.
I can't put it in.
Then I was thinking.
Oh, what should I do with this?
I'm dragging that fabric.
Just delaying time.
Just record it while thinking.
What to do?
Then I thought of a way.
Add flexibility.
Because other mattresses.
The ones that are made of mattresses.
I froze them.
Then.
Reversible.
Yes.
This effect is good.
After you add flexibility.
It will fold up and shrink by itself.
Then we go to adjust it again.
If you pull it down.
It will slide in directly.
Is it very convenient?
Yes.
Learned.
This effect is really good.
Yes.
It's faster.
Save time.
Yes.
Like me.
I just take a pin.
Then.
I have to pin it little by little.
To twist its shape.
I was thinking at that time.
Oh.
This.
If this is fixed.
Oh.
That should be a lot of work.
A little tired.
Yes.
It's really a little tired.
Then I will activate.
These virtual models.
Then.
Because I originally put this mattress.
When making this bed sheet.
I originally thought of using pins.
So I put his mattress.
Put it up a little bit.
Then we can start to simulate.
Select the bed in the middle.
Then pull it down little by little.
Well.
He can put this bed sheet tight.
Then.
If you want to make some adjustments later.
You can make some adjustments.
Jade hat.
Why?
Why is it a jade hat?
Is it very similar to a jade hat?
Then I was thinking.
What else is there on this bed?
After I finished making the bed sheet.
I went to look at other reference pictures again.
I started to look at that kind of.
More princess reference picture.
Then I saw.
They usually have that kind of small cushion.
It's a thin quilt.
Then I drew a new version.
Ready to make that cushion there.
Then the back is actually.
In the simulation.
In the calculation of these materials.
Then it is to draw his one airline line.
Just like what you just said.
We can draw some internal lines first.
Then when it comes to the Cologne layer.
Because of the phoenix line.
The phoenix line and the phoenix line.
There will be some phoenix lines automatically between the internal lines.
Then you give him some pressure.
Or use that conflict thickness.
It will have that kind of effect.
But I don't use pressure here.
I'll talk about this later.
It's just that I directly cut out the Cologne layer here.
I also prefer to use the Cologne layer function.
Yes, this function is very easy to use.
But it's a bit laggy.
If the surface is too high.
Yes, because if you add another surface.
Yes, there's nothing you can do about it.
Then I raised its conflict thickness a little bit.
And then because I think the CPU is too slow to decode.
I know I changed the GPU afterwards.
Or forget it.
Still use the GPU.
I was thinking.
No, I'm going to use the CPU for the whole video.
It's still a compromise.
I think the GPU is pretty good.
That's it.
Then use the GPU.
Then you can see.
Because.
I want to pause this.
Because of the conflict thickness.
It will form a little bit of this.
Just a little bit of this.
The effect.
And then sometimes we usually add pressure.
The effect of pressure is very pungent.
Yes, yes, yes.
Then the phoenix line.
The position of the phoenix line.
Because it's very tight.
So it's going to look like it's inflated.
But if you use the conflict thickness.
It's like flat cotton.
It's like that kind of cotton quilt in the summer.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's flat and thin.
And then there's a little bit of thickness in the middle.
So there are some.
This effect is great.
Yes, some of my friends.
If you like to use pressure.
He might not know.
You can achieve this effect with conflict thickness.
Because of the conflict thickness.
It itself is not so obvious.
An ebb and flow effect.
Where can I see this video?
If I post that live recording later.
I will post PR.
This is the pure image version.
To be honest, the pure image version.
In fact, there is no sound.
Then no one said.
This is the final version.
Then MD can make a leather material backpack?
Yes.
My voice is a little quiet.
It doesn't matter.
Just watch the video.
Then I want to make that quilt.
When I want to make a quilt.
I was thinking.
I want to make a quilt that folds over.
Because it doesn't look very good.
Then I drew the inner line.
Use folding arrangement tools.
Just fold this half.
In fact, because there are two layers of quilt.
If we do two layers first.
Then fold it.
Sometimes it will be difficult to identify.
Then you go to calculate.
Especially when opening GPU simulation.
It will be difficult to calculate.
So I usually fold it first.
After folding, I will do it.
This must be folded first.
Don't drag it by hand.
Because when I made quilts before.
I tried to drag it by hand.
It's too painful.
Yes.
I used to teach others at the earliest.
Still use that fixed needle to fold a whole piece.
Then fold it in two layers.
It really takes a lot of time.
It's better to fold it directly first.
Yes.
This new function is particularly easy to use.
Is this a new function?
This fold.
No.
No?
It has been there for many years.
It has been there since I started.
Some of them have only recently started to be used.
Really?
No.
It hasn't found yet.
Maybe I made fewer of these.
Then I just have to turn it over.
For example, the sleeves need to be turned around.
Yes.
Maybe I didn't pay attention to it before.
Then fold it.
Then you can start preparing for simulations.
Many people ask, why is md made into an old model?
Why?
Why is the MD programmer watching this video, I guess he's stupid.
Oh, and then I'll see the simulation and let him simulate it.
Actually, I used to really use less GPUs.
I don't know why, but in my heart, I still think the CPU simulation looks better.
And I don't want to fix it again.
So I used to use only GPUs.
But it's really too slow.
It's really better to use GPUs when making this kind of big furniture.
I think the CPU simulation is the same material.
The material of the CPU simulation is different from the material of the GPU simulation.
The quality of the material is different.
We are still optimizing the GPU simulation in the future.
And then I'll give him some pressure.
Let him do it.
I remember I just...
Didn't I record my part here?
I remember I had a part where he was too good at it.
And then I was stupid.
Oh, it should be coming soon.
It's coming.
And then I was...
My mom saw this part.
My mom asked me,
Why did you make this quilt look like this?
And then I was told by my mom.
I said, Mom, you keep looking.
You keep looking.
The next one will be good.
It will be good.
Because I put it back.
Yes, I'm talking.
And then I just think it's still a little rough.
But I want to forget it.
It doesn't matter.
If he touches it, let him touch it.
I'm going to adjust its physical material first.
Why am I adjusting the deformation intensity?
It's because I'm going to pause it.
There will be two clocks now.
It's this edge.
If your deformation intensity is too low,
Along this edge of the side.
Because the material properties are at this angle.
Or when it's on the edge of something else.
It will make a sharp cut.
And then the degree of sharpness is the deformation intensity.
So if you adjust the deformation intensity,
It won't be as obvious at this edge.
It's not easy to get that kind of edge.
It's just a very hard feeling.
I learned this.
This is what I normally do.
When you play a role, you may not encounter this problem.
And then this is in my tips and tricks.
No, it's in the video of the MD.
And then I looked at it again, and I felt that it was very bumpy.
I was thinking, oh, what should I do?
How can it be so bumpy?
Then I will click the arrow on the left side of the pressure.
You can enter specific numbers below yourself.
You can adjust, for example, 0.5, 0.8.
It will go down a little bit more.
Because sometimes some friends may not click the little arrow,
you can directly enter 1, and then 0 is not there, and then 1 is very bumpy.
So it can have a gap between 1 and 0.
Yes.
Yes, this is very important.
I saw a message saying, Master, Master, you're in bed.
You're in bed.
What is it?
This quilt is pregnant.
There is also character fabric at the back.
Do you want to explain it?
If you say it's the part of the絕肥, there will be a video later.
After that, I will upload a video of us recording.
Then I will make the pillow.
In fact, there is nothing to talk about the pillow here.
The pillow is very simple, just the pillow.
Just add pressure and then go.
Then I thought, I just made these pillows a little bumpy.
I just want to make some pillows for him.
He is like a candy.
It's round, and then the two ends are shrinked.
Then, like this one,
I might go to the arrangement board and the arrangement point by myself.
After that, I will draw a rectangular board.
Because it's very annoying to wrap the pillar directly with the board.
So I will make an arrangement board.
If you go directly to the arrangement board, it will be a little laborious, I think.
Yes.
Has the champion come out of the competition?
It seems that it hasn't come out yet.
It seems that it hasn't come out yet, I remember.
In fact, the result has already come out.
If the official has sent the notice, I will be stupid.
Then arrange it on this arrangement point.
Make the frame a little higher.
I am looking at it with my naked eyes.
If the size is similar, I will do it like this.
Then move it to this corner.
His chat says it's a corner.
Can MD make fried lotus powder?
I think fried lotus powder should be fine.
Fried lotus powder should not be very difficult.
Anyway, just take a few fabrics and pull them there.
A plate of fried lotus powder will be finished.
Then those meat slices.
What kind of vegetables?
Just use other materials to add.
I really can't think of this.
Yes.
How can there be a chat to ask this kind of question?
Is the video you recorded on QQ?
There is also on Bilibili.
Hot pot?
Hot pot should not work.
The pot outside the hot pot is fine.
The meat inside is not good.
I watched Substance before.
Someone made one with Substance.
Oh, yes.
I know.
He is a Chinese.
He did a great job.
Spicy hot pot.
I'm sick of it.
Yes.
The function of MD's coordinate axis should be strengthened.
What do you mean by the coordinate axis?
Because I think these three coordinates are often used.
Then I drew the line for him.
Then add the elasticity.
He will shrink by himself.
This is the kind of tightness on both sides.
This is like a sugar pillow.
In fact, I mentioned this method in the last competition video of Crytek.
Then I will reduce its strength.
Can MD predict a long rope with a cylinder?
Yes.
I will talk about that later.
Hot pot meat.
What is hot pot meat?
Can MD make hot pot meat?
It should not work.
I want to see sister backpack.
Well, next time.
Then I took advantage of everyone's absence.
When I didn't record it,
I put a rack with a board.
It's that kind of.
Generally speaking, it's more.
It's a girl's room.
They may have some pictures.
I put a frame on it.
Then I'm going to make the bedside table.
Why do you look hungry when you watch MD lessons?
That day my colleague came to me.
Big white rabbit milk candy.
Let me guess the taste of that big white rabbit milk candy.
I just know that the big white rabbit milk candy has a lot of flavors.
It was also posted on Weibo.
What has a mustard smell.
Then I looked at it at that time.
Mustard smell.
Will someone have a big white rabbit for mustard?
That's all a joke.
Thought it was a piece of mustard.
Oh, it's mustard.
Then I changed the coordinates.
Because before.
Because there is one here.
I want to tell you about it.
We have a screen coordinate.
Then only when using screen coordinates.
There is a suction function.
Just press shift.
It can absorb 45 degrees.
90 degrees.
I don't know why, but I don't know why there is no function development requirement for this.
Other coordinates can't be shifted 90 degrees, only the screen coordinates can be shifted 90 degrees.
Then I hooked up a board, because the curtains are all outside the pole.
Then if you go directly to make a board and then turn it over and sew it together, it will be very troublesome, so I hooked up another one.
I want to be able to lose the value, this seems to have mentioned the function development requirement before, but the program didn't reply.
Then adjust the position of these two boards a little bit.
Later I found out that there was a problem with the function development requirement.
Then adjust the position of these two boards.
When I saw it, I was like, I'm so dumb, did you see the simulation?
And after adding the simulation, the position of the board, I didn't put it in the right place
And it has some, what is it called, it has some cross-stitching problems
So I'll re-simulate it
Don't fully simulate it, and then activate the outer board
Because sometimes you have to simulate two boards at the same time, so it won't have this problem
Especially in cross-stitching, right?
Yes
Sometimes I think it's slower to simulate, so I'll simulate a small one first, and then a big one
And then copy one layer to the other side
And then after I finished making this bed curtain, oh, you can see that I suddenly became very fast
Because these are all unnecessary steps in the middle, and then I let it speed up
After that, because there are many bed curtains, because I want that kind of warm feeling
And then I can see the structure of this bed, so this bed curtain has to be pulled up like this
So I added a fixing pin to it, and then used the shrink tool to pull it up
This bed curtain will pull itself up
Use the shrink tool to pull it to the side
And then I think it's still not where I want it to be now
I'll use another shrink tool to let it go to the side
And then we'll add a fixing pin to the other side
And then put the shrink tool back
It's a bed curtain that pulls itself up
You don't have to pull the bed curtain by hand like this
Just pull it a little bit
This bed is scary
What's wrong with this bed?
Why is the bed scary?
Oh, the string is worn out
And there are such pieces and pillars that are directly inserted
If you wear it, you have to put that
Ah, don't go to the ward
Don't do it
And then on both sides
Then add a fixing pin on both sides
If you put the shrink back, it will pull itself up
You don't have to pull it by hand anymore
This style looks strange
Oh, no, you guys are like a ward
I can't go back
I feel like a ward now
It's like
Mainly they look at this curtain
It's a little bit
Don't do it
It's bleeding
After bleeding, it doesn't look like a ward anymore
Maybe because I haven't put the cover on it yet
It's a little bit like
It really feels like
It's like going to the hospital before the surgery
And then the ward when you're hospitalized
Hey, everyone, pay attention to your health
Because the season is crossing
I actually just wanted to cough today
I didn't have a chance to cough
Now it's my turn
I can finally cough quietly
After bleeding, go to the intensive care room
Don't do it
Are you sent by the enemy?
Why
I'm crying
Then I added the cover
Just do some cloth
Sew it on the top of this board
Then like GPU
It will appear like this on my picture
This kind of insertion problem
I may need to adjust it manually
Then I think this curtain behind me is a little too short
I'll use the screen to expand it first
Along with
Our cloth
Expand this side
Outside
It's going to be quarantined
No way
It shouldn't
Lack of oxygen bottle
Then use the folding tool to fold it directly
Because of our GPU simulation
Its cloth actually has a feeling of adhesion
That's why there will be
What's the problem with the previous insertions?
Generally speaking, we can harden this board
Then adjust it with a fixed needle
Just pull it out manually
In fact, these insertions are basically all
Because the board itself is attached to everything
So there will be such a problem
Sometimes I will
First use the CPU to calculate
Then let it open by itself
Then cut the GPU
Then continue to calculate
Yes
Sometimes I will
But because it's too laggy
I think it's too laggy
Forget it
Just look at the GPU
Very, very rough
Just adjust the area
Let's take a look
The frame is not made by Max
The frame is also made in AMD
It's made of board
Then pour out OBJ
Pour in again
Finally, use a fixed needle to adjust
This curtain
Then wait for its simulation to be almost stable
Then pause the simulation
Usually the GPU
It's okay to pull it out
It won't suck it back
Then finally
This should be
No
Let me take a look
Find my last rendering
My last
In fact, the rendering is still very warm
Don't say it's like a heavy needle
That room is really not like
I actually started
I didn't add this light when I was rendering
Then my boss told me
Why do you want to make such a dark room
Because it's very dark
I usually light up myself
I really like to have some very dark light
Then every time everyone gave feedback
Why is it so dark
Why can't I see anything
Can you add a light
Then I added a light
My boss said
Why do you want to add such a bright light
Can you make this light a little darker
Then I said
OK
I'll turn it down a little bit now
Then he said
OK
That's it
If you don't want to sound
Just right-click
There is a sound function
You can sound
Let's see
When the ping point is placed on the edge
It is possible to delete it separately
This is a bug
Then we are now
We have already applied for repair
It's terrible to change to cold light
In fact, I hit a cold light
It's just that I can't see it now
I hit a very small blue light
But because there is too much warm light
I really can't see it at all
The quilt is so strange
I don't care
I just want a very old quilt
Now let me go back to my desktop
If you have any questions
You can start asking questions now
Including asking Juefei
Ask me
All kinds of questions
Everyone likes to look at this screen
Just answer this screen
Do you have any questions?
While Juefei is turning
You can ask Juefei quickly
About some 3D
About what
Like sound
Like the role of MD
You can ask anything
Yes, because Juefei is really big
Very powerful
No, no, no
It's just
Magic magic
How do you sew clothes?
Just sew it directly
When will Juefei come out of the classroom?
This
Let's talk about this later
Is there a way?
Can MD make a leather silk backpack?
Yes
Is the person asking this question my colleague?
My colleague is busy with the backpack recently
It's like my colleague is asking secretly
Someone asked which company is Juefei
Juefei is now a freelancer
Yes, I didn't work in the company
And then I made some 5-pack bags at home
Mainly 5-pack bags
And then I will make some works myself
I feel a little free
Maybe Juefei can open his own art station
What?
Let's go to your page
Let's go to your work page
Okay
I think yours is better than mine
No
I also like the 2D
You are right
I want to make more 2D characters in the future
It's convenient
I think it's pretty good
How do you make the material into a steel object?
There is a hardening function on the right
It's to make it a little harder
Or you can go directly to the material properties
And change the physical properties to 9999
Let me see
Do you share your desktop?
Wait a minute
I share my desktop
Let me find it
Okay
It's not easy to make some clothes in real-time animation
I remember before Juefei
I saw Juefei made a...
Why didn't I see yours?
I need to cancel the sharing
How can I cancel it?
I think I should end the sharing first
Then you can share
Okay
It should be done
This is Juefei's set
The set in the lower left corner
Especially the set of girls
When I clicked on it
I was telling my colleague
This is so cute
It's different from other styles
Is it this one?
Yes
I need to turn on the accelerator
This one
Yes
Especially for girls
Very cute
Yes
I want to try this one
Because I want to try this one
The pose is a little bit complicated
And it has a little bit of wind
Or something like that
So I tried it
And I found that the effect is not bad
So I made this one
I like this style
I like the style
I like it
This style is really cool
I don't know how to explain it
It's like a mini-game
I have to see it
Yes
I can see it
I also saw that there is a Gianna in the lower left corner
Is that so?
Yes
This?
I thought it was Gianna
I didn't look carefully
But it seems to be a game
No
This is the original drawing of a big man
Then
I see the next one
It can't be turned down
It's a game original made by someone else's boss.
I simply restored it for him.
Is this a simple restoration?
This is obviously a big restoration.
No, this kind of cover and this part in the front,
including this part in the front,
are all solved with MD.
It's a dynamic solution.
I think it's easy to make hand-made stuff now.
Yes, I know there's a hand-made company working on it.
But I forgot what it's called.
I know there are some hand-made factories that make it.
Because it has some wind-blow and stuff like that.
Yes, and there's nothing else.
This is a game-made one.
Yes, I really like this one.
I think it's very cool.
It's...
I think it's a very cool hunter.
This is what it looks like.
It's really cool.
But I'm not a fan of it, so...
Actually, this is a bit of a hassle.
Because it doesn't have a reference picture.
You have to think about it and design it yourself.
How do you make the fabric better?
It's a bit of a hassle.
I'm not really satisfied with it.
Especially the dynamic and the whole thing.
And the whole screen.
The whole action doesn't have much tension.
That's how it feels.
So this is...
But the fabric layers are the most common.
Like this one.
It's all done in one file.
The collar is pressed under the leather.
The leather is pressed under the leather.
And then there's the fabric on top.
The layers are the most common.
And I thought the model's face was cool.
It's very handsome.
I was instantly attracted to this one.
I was like, wow, this is my soul.
It's so cool.
No, no, no.
This kind of collar is still easy to make.
It's easy to make.
And the rest, I think...
It's a bit more complicated than the MD.
I'm satisfied with the result.
If you make this kind of file,
how long do you think it will take to make it?
How long do you think it will take to make it?
Usually, it's like this.
If you don't have a clear reference,
for example, all the paper work,
all the artistic effects,
all the clothing,
and the beginning of these bags,
I can make them all by myself.
I think it can be done in a day.
That's fast.
It's still quite fast to make it in a day.
Yes, but sometimes,
there are more things that you have to satisfy.
For example, the language and the game requirements.
It might be a bit slower.
I think there are still a lot of very cool clothes in Juefei.
When I saw Artstation at the time,
I felt like...
Yes, this one and the others are all very cool.
I feel like...
Yes.
I think it's a good idea to deal with some of these things.
For example,
there's a bit of a skill-based style.
The skill is...
The head is a bit stuck.
It's a bit cool,
but it's based on some of the clothes in real life.
I think it's a good idea.
And I feel like I've done a lot of details.
Yes, this is mainly for reference.
I think it's very important.
Because we don't have the ability to design our own clothes.
We don't have the ability to design our own clothes.
After all, we still do 3D.
So, it's very important to find reference.
So, I've been practicing some design things lately.
I hope I can design some very cool clothes
and then do it myself.
Because I saw your previous...
The circle of friends also wrote,
ah, I'm going to do a tailor today.
Hahaha.
Hahaha, I saw the circle.
I thought, ah, I should be talking about MD.
Hahaha, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, I know that some game companies
will ask teachers to teach them how to make clothes
before they use MD.
They will ask teachers to teach them how to make clothes
and teach them the most basic half-hearted production methods.
Thank you.
I think these can be used.
But after all, it's not like real clothes.
I think it's more like a tailor's style.
Right?
There's one thing that when I do it,
I like to...
The final effect, let's set the final effect first.
After setting it, no matter how you do this board,
as long as the effect is almost the same, then it's OK.
I don't really care about this process.
For example, you must use this real tailor to cut it.
There's nothing to say.
Yes, so I think it's a little bit more powerful.
Just looking at the board,
it may not be so accurate,
but the final effect makes people feel very happy and satisfied.
My board is a little bit lazy.
My board is very lazy.
No, actually, when everyone uses MD,
they don't necessarily have to be the same as in real life.
Sometimes it will be set too much,
and then it's easy to limit yourself
to the effect that the original board can produce.
It's still...
It's like the method I used at the beginning,
which is to make a large model first,
and then use its UV to make a basic one.
I think it's not bad.
But...
It's more harmonious.
Yes, have you ever used OBJ directly into MD,
and then directly from the UV to the board?
It's the same principle.
There's no difference.
Yes, you just don't have to make some conclusions by hand.
It's just...
The premise of using this function is that the UV can't overlap.
Yes, you still have to...
The main reason why I made it manually is because
I'm afraid that the point is too messy.
I made it manually,
so I had to organize it as I bought it.
In fact, they're all the same. There's no difference.
What is the effect of the rigid effect I just mentioned?
I don't know if you're talking about hardening or something.
Sometimes hardening is just to make the board
easier to adjust, or to make it harder.
I'm begging you to teach me how to pay for it.
Here it is.
Here's the fire.
I don't know if you have any other...
No, no, no.
I'm still practicing anyway.
I always feel that I'm not satisfied with what I've done.
Because you can see that what I've done before,
for example, like this set,
I also feel that I'm not satisfied with what I've done before.
So I think I'll just keep doing it until I'm satisfied with it.
Or when I have some free time,
then I'll probably do these things.
In fact, I don't think I have much confidence in what I do.
I always feel that what I've done is not good.
I feel that other people have done a great job and I've done a bad job.
I think that's what everyone thinks.
I think that people who have done a great job
will also feel that they're not as good as others.
It's normal.
I think that because a lot of times
when we see the effects of what other people have done on the Internet,
we will...
we will say to ourselves in the company,
wow, look at this building.
Wow, this building.
Wow, this is so real.
It's so well done.
This fold, wow, it's so cool.
Or it's just that kind of style.
Some of them may be like what I saw before.
We have a friend in the group who posted one.
He's also a foreigner and a college student.
He did something very unique.
He's just very simple and good-looking.
Sometimes it's really hard to say good-looking.
Yes, good-looking.
I think good-looking is better than using a lot of software
or MD or something like that.
The final result has to be artistic.
After all, it's all about art.
It has to be good-looking.
How do you hit and solve hardware, equipment, and cloth on your body?
I usually just knock the model in.
Yes, just knock OBJ in.
It's like...
Of course, it's part of the body.
When you knock it in, you just solve the material.
It's no different from solving other things.
For example, you have a hard piece here.
Then you put your clothes in here, right?
The outside of the clothes is hard.
What is that hard surface?
I don't know.
Then you put it in your clothes.
It's like knocking it into part of the model.
Then you solve it.
How do you hit and solve the material in the equipment?
Hit and solve in the equipment?
One is that you have to modify the overall calculation.
That is, the distance between the cloth and the material.
One is this distance.
The other is that you have to lower the friction.
That is, the model of your equipment.
Then there is another point.
It may need to be a little thicker.
It may need to be a little bigger.
Then the rest of the words...
The rest of the words should be nothing.
That is to say, you still need to manually fix it.
Because your cloth can see that our model is the general model.
It's all the hair line is outwards.
You must not let the hair line go inwards.
Otherwise, the cloth will be stuck in it.
Then it won't come out all the time.
The hair line is outwards.
Then your equipment.
Don't make it too fine.
For example, this angle here.
Here is another angle, right?
Then there is another angle here.
Here is a very troublesome angle.
Don't make it too fine.
Otherwise, the cloth will be stuck in this place.
Then you can't calculate it.
Let's say you have a complex equipment.
You can simplify it a little bit.
Make a box.
Simplify it a little bit.
Put it in.
Then calculate again.
This will be a little better.
Yes.
You don't have to be so busy.
I don't want to use a real high-model.
I will simply make a box.
Yes.
If there is a problem with the insertion later in the game,
just fix it a little bit in the post-production.
How many years have you been using MD for free?
I'm very curious about this question.
I guess two years.
About one or two years.
About two years.
Then it's already very well used.
No.
I think there are still many places where MD can be done better.
Like the bed today.
The place where it folds over.
I don't even know this.
The place where I sit on the bed is actually a very troublesome place when I sit on the bed.
But it's done less.
Yes.
Sometimes, the size of the model ratio is not correct for the calculation and it will be very laggy.
I don't think I've ever encountered this problem.
I don't understand.
No, I've encountered this.
Because the model unit in MD...
For example, you have to make a...
For example, when you make a model come in,
it will let you choose...
Yes.
It will let you choose its unit.
Then your unit is best in your three-dimensional software.
My three-dimensional software unit is the same.
For example, I'm in Maya.
My unit is centimeters.
Then my whole thing is like this model.
Our height is 180 centimeters, right?
It's about the same.
This size is a character of 180 centimeters.
After you're done in here,
then my Maya unit is...
Here is a centimeter.
After you're in here,
then when we import it into MD,
our unit choice will be centimeter.
Because it has a real unit.
If your model is bigger,
it's equivalent to the size of your fabric.
Your fabric is very big.
Of course, you can calculate it.
It's very complicated, right?
The smaller your fabric is, the faster you can calculate it.
That's the problem.
If you have to make a big model,
then we just need to make it bigger.
It doesn't have to be so small.
Its effect is still very good.
Because its model is very large.
Because its diameter is...
I feel it's based on this flat space coordinate.
It will follow the diameter of your model
and make an automatic reduction.
That's how I feel.
He said...
What should we do with the unit of 1 meter?
The unit of 1 meter?
You can just import it into other lines.
The diameter of MD can only be 1 millimeter.
It can't be calculated by 1 to 1.
What do you mean?
I don't understand.
I usually...
Because I usually...
If the outside is a centimeter,
then I will import it into 1 meter as well.
I don't seem to have encountered such a problem.
If you import it into 1 meter,
then sometimes there will be some problems in the line of name.
Because of the difference in units.
But it seems that the problem is not very big.
I made a very small bag before.
As a result, the diameter of 1 millimeter is not enough.
In this case, you can use that bag first.
Use the unit...
Use a smaller unit.
Then when you export it,
you can export it with other units.
Or when you export it,
you can use the percentage of the percentage.
Sometimes you may use a smaller unit.
Or you can make the whole bag first.
The whole model is too small.
The whole model may be too small.
Yes.
Generally speaking,
for example, if you want to make a bag,
then the target speed you want is about the same as mine.
You estimate that it is about the same as mine.
Then your bag must be at least as big as it is now.
This is such a big bag.
Then you calculate the diameter.
If you need such a small fold,
then you can make such a big bag.
It doesn't have to be according to the proportion of the real world.
But I still recommend the real proportion of clothes and characters.
But if you have some special needs,
if you want to solve a small thing,
then you can enlarge this thing.
Then you can solve it.
Then when you import it,
you can test it first.
Is this diameter enough?
Oh.
I understand.
This ID is also a heavy customer.
Hehe.
See if there are any other friends who have questions.
It seems to be gone.
How do you do the wool material of the teacher?
Isn't it the same for hair?
Hair is a fabric, not a fabric.
It's a material or a special effect.
It's not a fabric.
What we care about is the direction of the fabric.
Hair can be made with XGene in Maya
or with substances in Substance.
How do you make the thread of the clothes?
The thread of the clothes?
Is it a sewing thread?
I don't know. I guess it is.
This one?
This one is still very simple.
There is a stitch in MD.
After you click on it...
Where is it?
It's right here.
After you click on it,
it will show the thread you want.
You can see that I have selected the thread
where there is a thread.
Here it is.
After you click on it,
it will show the thread.
You can adjust some parameters here.
Is the sewing thread a single model?
Is the sewing thread in MD OVJ?
Yes.
Let's take a look at this one.
Let's take a look at the sewing thread model I used.
Test 2.
Let's take a look at this one.
I see that the clothes are stuck in.
MD OVJ is not stuck in.
It is just floating on the surface.
Usually, those that are stuck in are used directly.
I think I have seen Substance before.
Substance.
When I was doing a live stream with MD OVJ,
I saw that Substance was able to do that.
Yes.
I don't think there is anything in here.
This sewing thread can be replaced.
It doesn't have to be a single sewing thread.
You can use it to make something like this.
Let me show you.
Artist.
Yes.
There is something here.
Artist.
Yes.
Here.
Let's do it then.
Yes.
I see.
Here.
Yes.
Let me get rid of this head.
Something like this.
This is also a layout in AMD.
Because I made this thing
into a single OBJ.
A single OBJ, and then I inserted it into AMD.
And then I used AMD's sewing function
to insert an OBJ.
And then I used a T for the sewing machine
to adjust its parameters
to get the right feeling of tiling.
And then I made something like this.
You can use this to make many patterns.
Including this kind of thing.
You can also export this kind of thing from AMD.
You don't need to do it manually.
But you can do it manually.
You can also do it in AMD.
But I personally think that this kind of flat,
flat,
you can do it in AMD.
Including this kind of seam line,
Is there a playback?
Yes, there is.
There is a playback.
How does the line of the waist segmentation
work?
This?
What does this mean?
You can see that this is frozen.
Just take a board
and freeze it.
And you'll be fine.
It's fine, it's not difficult.
So I think it'll work.
It's not a problem?
Yes.
Let's see if there are any questions.
As it's late now.
I feel like it's a lot of trouble for Jelfie.
Because I think a lot of the questions
this time were answered by Jelfie.
He's so happy and happy.
But he has a few time to answer his own questions.
Did AMD replace Max or Microsoft?
Not at all.
I've never thought of that.
It's impossible.
Because the 3D industry can't say that any software can cover all the things a software can do.
I think all software is complementary.
It's just the difference of the weight of the stand.
Actually, everyone is...
Right.
Yes.
If you really want to do a project,
there are really a lot of software to use.
Yes.
You can see that there are basically a lot of software here.
There's everything.
Yes.
AMD's top features are even better than Huawei's.
AMD top is still thinking about how to optimize it.
ZB's cloth is Pinduoduo.
Pinduoduo is Pinduoduo.
Speaking of this,
before my little friend said that ZB and Blender have made some fabric calculations.
I think it's not about which one is particularly good or which one is not.
I think both are making progress.
It's actually quite normal for them to make these fabric calculations afterwards.
But I think the direction of the face is different anyway.
Yes.
It may be a little bit more concise.
I think.
Yes.
It's more of a simple way to play, but MD is more professional and more complex.
There's always a gap between the belt and the belt.
I think there's usually a gap between the belt and the belt.
If there's really a gap between the belt and the belt...
Sometimes there's a gap.
Maybe the belt is too tight.
Maybe it's better to set a level.
It doesn't really matter.
Just go back and take a break.
It won't be a big problem.
I feel like it's almost 2 hours.
I will upload the rest of the videos to BB.
When I upload the videos, I will add your BB account.
And you.
I will also put the address of your Art Station in the comments.
I hope everyone can pay more attention to Jeff.
Because I think he's really good.
And everyone has a lot of questions.
I'm sure there will be a lot of questions.
I'll need to find you later.
I'll add your BB account.
Or your Art Station.
Everyone can contact you.
Because I don't want to give you too much information.
I don't want to give you too much burden.
So I didn't write your email address on it.
But now I have it on the top right corner.
I just want to remind you.
You received a lot of emails.
It's okay.
I'll think of a way to cover it up later.
I'll cut this one off at the end.
That's all.
Yeah.
I'll post the ones in the BB approach later.
You guys can pay attention.
And pay attention to that BB account.
And pay attention to Jeff's BB account.
And I hope to cooperate again soon.
Because since Jeff joined the stream,
the channel has showed up.
And there are so many people here to help answer the questions.
This feeling is really cool.
Okay, that's it for today.
If you have any questions,
you can leave them in the comments below this video.
If I see them, I will reply.
As long as I can reply,
I will read all the comments and messages.
I will reply to all of them.
That's it for today.
Thank you, Juefei.
It's late.
It's okay.
Thank you.
That's it for today.
Bye.